let savollar29 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "to advertise",
        answer: "A. reklama qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. reklama qilmoq",
            "B. sotib olmoq",
            "C. rejalashtirmoq",
            "D. qurmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to assign",
        answer: "B. topshirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. rad etmoq",
            "B. topshirmoq",
            "C. tugatmoq",
            "D. unutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "audience",
        answer: "C. auditoriya",
        options: [
            "A. aktyor",
            "B. musobaqa",
            "C. auditoriya",
            "D. murabbiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "breakfast",
        answer: "A. nonushta",
        options: [
            "A. nonushta",
            "B. tushlik",
            "C. kechki ovqat",
            "D. gazak"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "competition",
        answer: "D. musobaqa",
        options: [
            "A. mashg'ulot",
            "B. tomoshabin",
            "C. qiyinchilik",
            "D. musobaqa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "cool",
        answer: "B. salqin",
        options: [
            "A. issiq",
            "B. salqin",
            "C. iliq",
            "D. quruq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to gain",
        answer: "A. olmoq",
        options: [
            "A. olmoq",
            "B. yo'qotmoq",
            "C. saqlab qolmoq",
            "D. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "importance",
        answer: "C. ahamiyat",
        options: [
            "A. boylik",
            "B. zavq",
            "C. ahamiyat",
            "D. quvonch"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "knowledge",
        answer: "A. bilim",
        options: [
            "A. bilim",
            "B. kuch",
            "C. zaiflik",
            "D. xotira"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "major",
        answer: "D. katta",
        options: [
            "A. kichik",
            "B. ahamiyatsiz",
            "C. oson",
            "D. katta"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "mean",
        answer: "C. yovuz",
        options: [
            "A. do'stona",
            "B. baxtli",
            "C. yovuz",
            "D. qayg'uli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "to prefer",
        answer: "A. afzal ko'rmoq",
        options: [
            "A. afzal ko'rmoq",
            "B. rad etmoq",
            "C. unutmoq",
            "D. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "president",
        answer: "B. prezident",
        options: [
            "A. talaba",
            "B. prezident",
            "C. o'qituvchi",
            "D. do'st"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "progress",
        answer: "C. rivojlanish",
        options: [
            "A. orqaga qaytish",
            "B. muvaffaqiyatsizlik",
            "C. rivojlanish",
            "D. turg'unlik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "respect",
        answer: "A. hurmat",
        options: [
            "A. hurmat",
            "B. nafrat",
            "C. befarqlik",
            "D. yoqtirmaslik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "rich",
        answer: "B. boy",
        options: [
            "A. kambag'al",
            "B. boy",
            "C. tejamkor",
            "D. saxiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "skill",
        answer: "A. mahorat",
        options: [
            "A. mahorat",
            "B. bilmaslik",
            "C. tasodif",
            "D. baxtsizlik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "somehow",
        answer: "C. qandaydir",
        options: [
            "A. aniq",
            "B. shubhasiz",
            "C. qandaydir",
            "D. aniq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "strength",
        answer: "B. kuch",
        options: [
            "A. zaiflik",
            "B. kuch",
            "C. mo'rtlik",
            "D. yumshoqlik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "to vote",
        answer: "A. ovoz bermoq",
        options: [
            "A. ovoz bermoq",
            "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "C. rad etmoq",
            "D. tark etmoq"
        ]
    }
];
